<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Design Material</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="baby_girl_info">Baby \"Ms. Dainty\" Girl is an American calico cat, grass eater, pool walker,
        and lizard killer. She is a strong, independent female who don\'t need no man, and is
        easily identified by a prominent mohawk and bald
        spot on her head. Despite her friendliness toward humans, Baby Girl has earned
        a reputation as a fearsome bug and lizard eater, and her claws are sharp enough
        to scratch diamond. [citation needed] She used to enjoy wedging herself into tight
        places, but these days, she roams the great outdoors, bringing <strike>
        terror and bloodshed </strike> love and admiration wherever she goes.
    </string>

    <string name="baby_girl_likes">Wet food, going outside, licking things, eating bugs and lizards,
        laying in her chair, walking around the pool, climbing things, chasing her brother, face scratches.
    </string>

    <string name="baby_girl_dislikes">Being picked up, having to stay inside, water, dogs, being groomed
    by someone</string>

    <string name="rocko_info">Rocko, aka Rocko Bear, is an American orange and white shorthair cat,
        dragonfly slayer, and snack enthusiast. He has a well-known default-deny policy toward
        human interaction, which means that for those lucky enough to earn Rocko\'s trust, there is
        much Rocko love to be had. He can often be found outside being chased by his sister,
        Baby Girl. A clean Rocko is a sad Rocko. He will often dirty himself up by laying in the
        dirt, and may just snack on a bug he comes across while he\'s at it. Remember, if he claws you
        when you rub his belly, that means he loves you.
     </string>

    <string name="rocko_likes">Treats, getting dirty, splashing water around, belly rubs, eating bugs,
    playing in the rain, pink mice</string>

    <string name="rocko_dislikes">Most people, loud noises, dogs, being clean</string>

    <string name="title_activity_cat_detail">CatDetailActivity</string>
</resources>
